# JORDAN YOUNG

## **FULL-STACK ENGINEER / UX DESIGNER**

+61 405 128 569

Sydney, NSW

https://jordan-young.com

#### SUMMARY

With 2 years of commercial experience, I bring a strong understanding of core web technologies (HTML, CSS, Javascript) and solid experience working with modern frameworks (Angular) to develop interactive applications integrated with cloud back-ends (Node.js, AWS).

My interests lie in bridging the gap between creativity and functionality. I enjoy building responsive, user-friendly interfaces and crafting smooth animations to create transformative user experiences. As a fast learner capable of mastering new tools on the job, I am keen to grow my expertise within a team that values mentorship, collaboration, and continuous development.

I aim to deepen my expertise as a **creative engineer** who understands the technical aspects and strategic design thinking needed to deliver innovative solutions that are mesmerising to the eye.

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

FEB 2023 - OCT 2024

## Front-end Developer Analyst

Accenture Song

- Contributed to end-to-end project delivery including development, SIT, UAT, and go-live support for enterprise web applications.
  Ensured seamless transitions between phases with rigorous testing and documentation.
- Built responsive, high-performance user interfaces using HTML, JavaScript/TypeScript (Angular), achieving full cross-browser and mobile responsiveness using modern CSS techniques and adherence to accessibility standards
- Collaborated with back-end engineers to design and implement REST APIs, ensuring efficient data flow between Angular front-ends and CMS/backend systems.
- Partnered with designers in workshops to create Figma prototypes and design systems, bridging technical feasibility with user experience requirements
- Presented regular demos and updates to align cross-functional teams and clients on component functionality and UX decisions.
- Led a small team to design and develop a Salesforce Experience Cloud website used in Accenture's showcase at Dreamforce 2023 to over 100 global clients.
- Designed user journey maps, personas and graphic artefacts to contribute to strategy development for client RFPs.

MAY 2021 - DEC 2022

## **Content Specialist**

Mastercard

- Updated and maintained the Mastercard Rewards catalogue using **HTML** and **CSS**, ensuring consistent product display and visual alignment across all listings.
- Managed backend database for Mastercard Rewards catalogue using a mix of SQL queries and Excel lookup functions.
- Implemented structured QA guidelines and maintained QA reporting system.
- · Lead weekly content meetings to discuss team workflow and capacity.

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

#### Salesforce Administrative Intern

Rugby Australia

- Automated reports and dashboards in Salesforce Marketing Cloud.
- · Streamlined data imports and cleanups using Dataloader.

SEPT 2019 - DEC 2019

#### **IT Administrative Intern**

Rugby Australia

- Provided L1 tech support and hardware troubleshooting.
- Managed Microsoft Active Directory user accounts and permissions.

# JORDAN YOUNG

## **FULL-STACK ENGINEER / UX DESIGNER**

+61 405 128 569

Sydney, NSW

https://jordan-young.com

### **EDUCATION**

MAR 2018 - FEB 2024

## **Bachelor of Computing Science (Honours)**

University of Technology Sydney (UTS)

· Major in Interaction Design.

• Conducted honours research in **AI**, analysing the efficacy of Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) on 3D model generation.

• Utilised containerisation technology (Docker) to create testing and training environments.

• Modified existing architectures using **Python** to train GAN models to generate 3D meshes and voxels.

• Performed quantitative and qualitative analysis on results.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-end technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Angular, React (learning), SCSS, jQuery

Back-end technologies: Python, SQL, Node.js/ExpressJS

Tools & Platforms: Figma, Git, Docker, AWS Lambda, ApiGateway and EC2

Additional skills: UI/UX design and research, Generative AI, Agile project management, Data analytics

## CO-CURRICULARS

Volunteering: Eat Up. Australia, ABCN Innovate mentoring, Fifty5-Five buddy program